(Amy:)I make compromises for you all the time.
(Amy:)Just this once, can't we find something
that we're both happy with?
(Sheldon:)Fine. How about one of the most beguiling
and influential couples of the 20th century?
(Sheldon:)Hewlett and Packard.
(Sheldon:)Dibs on Hewlett.
You wanna be Hewlett?
- Anybody home?
- Hey, what are you doing here?
(Penny:)I just thought I'd stop by and say hello.
(Leonard:)What a nice surprise.
- I don't think you've seen my lab before.
- I know, it's long overdue. What you doing?
(Penny:)Better not be building a robot girlfriend.
(Leonard:)No. Although, Howard was making some
strides in that area until he met Bernadette.
- What, you're kidding?
- No.
(Leonard:)Now the Lisatronic 3000 just sits in a box,
waiting for the phone to ring.
(Penny:)- What's going on in here?
- No, no, no, don't look in there.